Previously on the show. Paddi, who has a sprout growing on his head,
ความเดิมตอนที่แล้ว แพดดี้ เจ้าแกะที่มีต้นอ่อนงอกอยู่บนหัว
is responsible for making weather fruit.
รับหน้าที่ผลิตลูกสี่ฤดู
His misunderstanding towards Weslie gave Wolffy a chance to take advantage of.
เรื่องที่แพดดี้เข้าใจเวสลี่ผิด ทำให้วูฟฟี่ฉวยโอกาสนี้เล่นงานเขา
After finding out the truth,
หลังจากที่ได้รู้ความจริง
Paddi felt guilty and made the weather fruit attack Wolffy.
แพดดี้รู้สึกผิด จึงผลิตลูกสี่ฤดูเพื่อใช้ต่อสู้กับวูฟฟี่
What will happen next?
เรื่องราวจะเป็นอย่างไรต่อไปนะ
"Flying Island: The Sky Adventure: The Fruits of Hardwork."
"แกะน้อยสุดกวนกับหมาป่าจอมป่วน ตอน ผลไม้ที่ได้จากการทำงานหนัก"
What to do? Look at the condition of the weather tree.
ทำยังไงดีล่ะ ดูสภาพต้นสี่ฤดูนี่สิ
And there are so many orders!
ออเดอร์สั่งซื้อเข้ามาก็เยอะแยะเต็มไปหมด!
Don't worry. Paddi and I will help out the best we can.
ไม่ต้องห่วงฮะ แพดดี้กับผมจะช่วยอย่างเต็มที่เลยฮะ
Paddi!
แพดดี้!
Looks like he has a cold.
ดูเหมือนเขาจะเป็นหวัดนะ
Doctor, we've noticed too.
หมอฮะ เราก็สังเกตเห็นเหมือนกัน
But if you take your medicine on time, you'll be fine in no time.
ถ้านายกินยาตรงเวลา ไม่นานก็จะหายดีเองแหละ
Medicine? Doctor, I'm not sick!
ยาเหรอฮะ หมอฮะ ผมไม่ได้ป่วยซะหน่อย!
Look, I'm feeling great.
ดูสิฮะ ผมรู้สึกดีสุดๆ ไปเลย
Paddi, listen to the doctor and take your medicine.
แพดดี้ เชื่อหมอและกินยาเถอะนะ
Exactly! You'll feel better afterward.
นั่นสิ กินแล้วเดี๋ยวก็จะรู้สึกดีขึ้นนะ
I don't want medicine!
ผมไม่อยากกินยานี่นา!
Doctor, I've caught a cold. Can you give me some medicine?
หมอฮะ ผมเป็นหวัด หมอช่วยจ่ายยาให้หน่อยได้ไหมฮะ
Just take this pill and your sickness will be gone in no time.
กินยานี้ซะและอีกไม่นานก็จะหายดีนะ
I don't want medicine!
ผมไม่อยากกินยา!
Paddi.
แพดดี้
So amazing!
วิเศษไปเลย!
Who knew my nose would clear up just after taking the medicine.
ใครจะไปคิดว่ากินยาแล้วจมูกจะโล่งขนาดนี้
The medicine is clearly very effective.
เห็นได้เลยนะว่ายาได้ผลจริงๆ
Of course. If you take your medicine, you'll be fine in two days.
แน่นอนสิ กินยาสักสองวันก็จะหายดีเองแหละ
Doctor, why didn't you say it earlier?
ทำไมหมอไม่บอกก่อนหน้านี้ล่ะฮะ
But no worries, I'll go explain it to Paddi now.
แต่ไม่ต้องห่วงฮะ ผมจะไปบอกแพดดี้เดี๋ยวนี้แหละ
Paddi, I'm telling the truth.
แพดดี้ ฉันพูดเรื่องจริงนะ
This cold medicine is really effective!
ยานี้แก้หวัดได้จริงๆ นะ
You'll recover very soon if you take it.
ถ้านายกินยานี้นะ อีกไม่นานก็จะหายดี
Okay, fine.
โอเค ก็ได้ฮะ
I need to sleep now. I'll take it later.
ตอนนี้ผมอยากนอนก่อน ไว้ค่อยกินทีหลังนะ
Okay, rest first then.
ก็ได้ งั้นก็นอนพักก่อนละกัน
I've put the pills on the table.
ฉันวางยานี้ไว้บนโต๊ะนะ
Remember to take it when you wake up.
นายตื่นนอนแล้วอย่าลืมกินยานี้นะ
I'm not gonna take it.
ผมไม่กินยานั่นหรอก
That patient had such a crazy reaction after taking it.
คนไข้นั่นกินยาแล้วท่าทางก็เพี้ยนๆ ไปเลย
Thinking of it makes me scared.
แค่คิดก็ทำให้กลัวซะแล้วสิ
How is Paddi doing?
แพดดี้จะเป็นยังไงบ้างนะ
Looks like he's still unwilling to take it.
ดูเหมือนว่าจะยังไม่อยากกินยาอยู่ดี
Oh no, we're in trouble.
ไม่นะ เราแย่แน่ๆ เลย
There are still 1,000 incomplete fruit orders.
ยังเหลืออีก 1,000 ออเดอร์ที่ยังไม่เสร็จเลย
And now Paddi is sick. What should I do?
แล้วตอนนี้แพดดี้ก็ป่วย
How about I go explain to the customers,
ผมลองไปอธิบายให้ลูกค้าฟังดีไหมฮะ
see if we can give them a partial order first?
ลองดูว่าเราจะส่งของบางส่วนให้ก่อนได้ไหม
Fantastic!
วิเศษไปเลย!
The weather fruit got here on schedule.
ลูกสี่ฤดูที่สั่งมาส่งตรงเวลาเป๊ะเลย
How come there're so few?
แล้วทำไมถึงมีอยู่แค่นี้ล่ะ
I'm so sorry. There's a situation at the factory.
ผมขอโทษครับ คือเกิดเรื่องที่โรงงานครับ
Please use these first.
กรุณาใช้พวกนี้ไปก่อนนะครับ
It's hard to keep my business going without enough weather fruits.
ถ้ามีลูกสี่ฤดูไม่มากพอ มันก็ยากที่จะทำธุรกิจนี้ต่อไปนะ
My deepest apologies. We'll deliver the rest in two days.
ผมขอโทษจริงๆ ครับ อีกสองวันเราจะส่งของที่เหลือให้นะครับ
Oh, I see.
โอเค เข้าใจแล้ว
Okay, you promised, two days.
โอเค นายสัญญาแล้วนะ อีกสองวันก็ได้
Hello, is anyone there? I'm here to deliver the weather fruits.
หวัดดีครับ มีใครอยู่ไหมครับ ผมมาส่งลูกสี่ฤดูครับ
Did you send the wrong package?
คุณส่งของผิดรึเปล่า
I ordered more weather fruits than this.
ฉันสั่งลูกสี่ฤดูไปมากกว่านี้นะ
I'm sorry, there's a problem at the factory.
ขอโทษครับ ที่โรงงานเกิดเรื่องน่ะครับ
We'll deliver the rest in two days.
อีกสองวันเราจะส่งของที่เหลือให้นะครับ
Mum... I want ice cream.
แม่... หนูอยากกินไอศกรีม
We don't have enough weather fruits now.
ตอนนี้เรามีลูกสี่ฤดูไม่พอจ้ะ
How about we have some in two days? I'll see you again.
อีกสองวันเราค่อยกินไอศกรีมดีไหม ฉันจะได้เจอคุณอีกแน่นะ
I'll deliver the rest as soon as I can.
ผมจะจัดส่งของที่เหลือให้เร็วที่สุดเท่าที่จะทำได้
I've finally dealt with the customers, for now.
ในที่สุดผมก็คุยตกลงกับลูกค้าได้แล้วฮะ
But the rest needs to be produced in two days. What should we do?
แต่เราต้องผลิตผลไม้ที่เหลือให้ได้ภายในสองวัน เราจะทำยังไงดีล่ะฮะ
Thank you, Weslie.
ขอบใจนะ เวสลี่
I'll think of something for the rest.
ฉันจะลองหาทางออกเรื่องผลไม้ที่เหลือเองจ้ะ
Why don't you go check on Paddi?
ทำไมนายไม่ลองไปดูแพดดี้หน่อยล่ะ
I wonder if Paddi's cold recovered or not.
สงสัยจังว่าแพดดี้หายเป็นหวัดรึยัง
Turns out Paddi didn't take a single pill.
กลายเป็นว่าแพดดี้ไม่ได้กินยาเลยสักเม็ด
Paddi, get up and eat candy.
แพดดี้ ตื่นขึ้นมากินลูกอมเถอะ
If you don't eat it, I will.
ถ้านายไม่กินล่ะก็ ฉันกินเองนะ
No way. No reaction from him at all.
ไม่มีทาง ไม่มีปฏิกิริยาตอบรับจากแพดดี้เลย
How refreshing!
สดชื่นอะไรอย่างนี้!
Turns out the pill is just like mint candy.
กลายเป็นว่ายาก็เหมือนลูกอมรสมิ้นต์นี่เอง
Where did Paddi go?
แพดดี้หายไปไหนนะ
Excuse me, have you seen a goat come here to buy snacks?
โทษทีครับ คุณเห็นแกะมาซื้อขนมที่นี่บ้างไหมฮะ
I haven't.
ฉันไม่เห็นนะ
Have you seen a goat about this high and a little chubby?
คุณเห็นแกะจ้ำม่ำๆ ตัวสูงเท่านี้มาที่นี่ไหมฮะ
Paddi!
แพดดี้!
Paddi, where are you?
แพดดี้ นายอยู่ที่ไหน
Are you looking for me?
ตามหาฉันอยู่เหรอ
Sorry, wrong person.
ขอโทษทีครับ ทักผิดคนฮะ
Paddi!
แพดดี้!
Let's go look somewhere else.
ไปลองหาที่อื่นกันเถอะ
All right.
ก็ได้
Paddi!
แพดดี้!
Paddi, where did you go?
แพดดี้ นายหายไปไหนเนี่ย
Could it be that he was captured by Wolffy?
หรือว่าเขาจะถูกวูฟฟี่จับตัวไปแล้ว
Don't worry... We will definitely find him.
ไม่ต้องห่วง... ในที่สุดเราก็ต้องหาเขาเจอสิ
Just in time.
ทันเวลาพอดีเลย
How could he hide and sleep here?
แพดดี้แอบมานอนอยู่ที่นี่ได้ไงเนี่ย
Weslie, look over there.
เวสลี่ ดูทางโน้นสิ
Weather fruits?
ลูกสี่ฤดูเหรอ
995, 996, 997...
995 996 997...
I'm just missing two rain fruits and a wind fruit,
ยังขาดแค่ลูกสายฝนสองลูก กับลูกสายลมอีกหนึ่งลูก
then the orders are all complete.
แค่นั้นก็จะครบทุกออเดอร์แล้ว
Everyone will be so surprised when they find out.
ถ้าทุกคนรู้ข่าวนี้เข้าจะต้องเซอร์ไพรส์แน่ๆ
998, 999...
998 999...
Keep it up, Paddi!
พยายามต่อไปนะ แพดดี้
One thousand! Finished!
หนึ่งพันลูก! เสร็จเรียบร้อย!
Paddi! You finished all the orders alone.
แพดดี้ นายผลิตผลไม้เองได้ครบทุกออเดอร์เลย
You're amazing!
นายสุดยอดมากๆ เลย!
Really? Look!
จริงเหรอฮะ ดูนี่นะ!
I even made such a big wind fruit.
ผมผลิตลูกสายลมลูกใหญ่เบ้อเริ่มนี่เองเลยนะ
Watch out!
ระวังนะ!
Weather fruits!
ลูกสี่ฤดู!
Paddi, don't go over. It's dangerous!
แพดดี้ อย่าไปทางนั้น มันอันตรายนะ!
Are you guys okay?
ทุกคนโอเคกันไหม
What do we do?
เราจะทำยังไงกันดีล่ะ
What to do? The weather tree won't dry up and die, right?
ทำยังไงดีล่ะ ต้นสี่ฤดูคงไม่แห้งตายใช่ไหมฮะ
Don't cry. Take your pills and get better first.
อย่าร้องไห้เลย กินยารักษาตัวเองให้หายดีก่อนเถอะ
So refreshing!
สดชื่นอะไรอย่างนี้!
I didn't know the cold medicine is this delicious.
ไม่ยักรู้ว่ายาแก้หวัดจะอร่อยขนาดนี้
If I had known, I would have...
ถ้ารู้มาก่อนนะ ผมคงจะ...
Perfect!
เยี่ยมไปเลยจ้ะ!
The weather tree's back to life.
ต้นสี่ฤดูเจริญงอกงามอีกครั้งแล้วจ้ะ
What?
อะไรนะ
How did the weather tree get better all of a sudden?
ทำไมอยู่ๆ ต้นสี่ฤดูกลับมาแข็งแรงได้ล่ะ
Good question.
เป็นคำถามที่ดีนะ
Those weather fruits exploded, causing a thunderstorm.
ลูกสี่ฤดูที่ระเบิดนั่นทำให้เกิดพายุฝนฟ้าคะนอง
The dead branches got struck by lightning and fell off coincidentally.
กิ่งไม้ที่ตายแล้วบังเอิญถูกฟ้าผ่าและหล่นลงมา
Then the wind blew away the dry leaves.
จากนั้นลมก็พัดเอาใบไม้แห้งปลิวไป
The rain fruit coincidentally showered the whole weather tree.
ลูกสายฝนทำให้เกิดฝนตกไปทั่วต้นสี่ฤดู
Thus, the weather tree has been reborn.
ด้วยเหตุนี้จึงทำให้ต้นสี่ฤดูฟื้นคืนชีวิตอีกครั้ง
What a coincidence!
ช่างบังเอิญอะไรอย่างนี้!
Yes, we're that lucky.
ใช่ เราโชคดีนะเนี่ย
I didn't think that I did something good.
ผมไม่คิดว่าตัวเองทำความดีอะไรเลยฮะ
But the 1,000 orders for weather fruits are not done yet.
แต่ลูกสี่ฤดูอีก 1,000 ออเดอร์ ก็ยังไม่เสร็จอยู่ดีนะ
Why am I always the one that suffers?
ทำไมต้องงานเข้าผมคนเดียวตลอดเลยอ่ะ